Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Video and Film Works, 1975-2015; 79.9 Linear Feet in 42 cassette boxes, 36 record cartons, 8 manuscript boxes, 4 LP boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 2 flat files; 195 VHS; 133 U-matic; 111 Hi8; 85 audiocassettes; 70 MiniDV; 14 Half_Inch_Video_Reel; 6 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 4 1_Inch_Video_Reel
  - Subseries II.D: Works by Date, 1975-2015
    - Compilation Tape -- "Hello Austria," A.E. Bla Bla, Bla, A Live Laser, ID / It's Dance, undated (Box 140, Vhs 437_1863)
    - Compilation Tape -- Birds and Dolphins, Tape 61 TC 21, John Cage Interview, undated (Box 142, U-matic 437_2118)
    - Compilation Tape -- Window of Chance, Art Around the Park, undated (Box 143, U-matic 437_2121)
    - Compilation Tape -- 30 Seconds, Mouth / Eye / MoMA, A-Z (5mm) How She Sees It, Branca Slides, undated (Box 143, Vhs 437_2133)
    - Compilation Tape -- Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, AU, AZ, film off wall, A with smoke, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1811)
    - Compilation Tape -- ID / It's Dance, It's a Live Laser, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1523)
    - Compilation Tape -- ID / It's Dance, It's a Live Laser "Hello Austria", undated (Box 131, Vhs 437_1653)
    - Compilation Tape -- New York States, Sun Daze Away, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, Belize, undated (Box 114, Vhs 437_1031)
    - Compilation Tape -- Birds, Underwater dolphins, Kids, undated (Box 92, Hi8 437_1319)
    - Compilation Tape -- R. L., China, Boys, Christ, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1152)
    - Compilation Tape -- Samples, undated (Box 153, U-matic 437_0045)
    - Compilation Tape -- Trims, undated (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0172)
    - Compilation Tape -- Xi'ang, Marbles projections, Sun Daze Away, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1852)
    - Compilation Tape -- Yonkers, Alphabets, Static cam #1, Color kids, undated (Box 92, Hi8 437_1315)
    - Compilation Tape -- Performance art and video art, Cast Iron E+T, undated (Box 140, Vhs 437_1857)
    - Compilation Tape -- Video samples, theme song, "Hello Vienna," Valentine's Day, credits, Bla Bla, Bla edit, undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1443)
    - Compilation Tape -- It's a Live Laser, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, AEIOU, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1212)
    - Compilation Tape -- Sun Daze Away, New York States, Glenn Branca Symphony No. 4 / Physics, Windows of Chance / Change, undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1452)
    - Computer animation, Brucknerhaus, undated (Box 104, Hi8 437_2223)
    - "Dolphins", undated (Box 153, U-matic 437_0043)
    - "Dolphins and Underwater Dolphins", undated (Box 100, Hi8 437_2062)
    - Downtown, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1475)
    - Eat Your Words, undated
      - "Pink, Letter by Letter, U's, Credits" (Box 123, U-matic 437_1222)
      - "Perri Peltz" (Box 123, U-matic 437_1224)
      - First Edit, Original (Box 144, U-matic 437_2167)
    - Edit for Paul Friedlander, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1731)
    - "Fire" section, #1 raw matter, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1169)
    - "Hello Vienna," "Hello Austria", undated (Box 129, U-matic 437_1666)
    - Hi8 Workshop and Letter Edit, Forakis Base, Age and Chance at Suzi NYC, undated (Box 98, Hi8 437_2002)
    - International Super 8 Night, Club 57, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Joannie's Work, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1760)
    - Kachts in der Stadtden Video Stills, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "L'amica Americana Video Donna" Poster, Teatro Viola, Bologna, undated (Flat-file-folder 4)
    - Lips, XOCC, Pauline, Jack Waters, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2333)
    - Live TV, undated (Box 151, Half inch video reel 437_0026)
    - "Moon with Clouds", undated (Box 153, U-matic 437_0042)
    - "Ocean", undated (Box 91, Hi8 437_1306)
    - Nik, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1805)
    - Nam June Paik with Steadycam, undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1434)
    - Notes, undated (Box 126, U-matic 437_1239)
    - NY Nation -- Release Form, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Poem video collab, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1492)
    - Production Master, undated (Box 91, Dat 437_2289)
    - Program #1, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1840)
    - Raw footage tape #3, undated (Box 119, U-matic 437_1118)
    - Raw material outside window, undated (Box 118, U-matic 437_1107)
    - Reading at table, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1160)
    - Road Rant with Lydia Lunch by Merrill Aldighier, undated (Box 120, Vhs 437_1197)
    - Scanner Dance, undated
      - Scanner / Rapidots (Box 151, Half inch video reel 437_0023)
      - 2 (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_0029)
      - Scanner / Trails (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_0035)
    - "Sex", undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1832)
    - Side A: Line symphony / Side B: Because I would not stop for death (take I), undated (Box 85, Audiocassette 437_0862)
    - "Sign Language" 8mm, tape #20, undated (Box 119, U-matic 437_1117)
    - Skidmore, undated (Box 125, U-matic 437_1236)
    - SKT Faces (M), undated (Box 152, Half inch video reel 437_0038)
    - Steve Speer Animations, undated
      - Video (Box 138, Vhs 437_1813)
      - Video (Box 138, Vhs 437_1812)
    - Opera -- Tape #4, 6, 7, Excerpts from #5, Edit, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1121)
    - Tape #7, Assorted Footage, undated (Box 127, U-matic 437_1605)
    - Terry TV, Art Studio, undated (Box 81, Audiocassette 437_0674)
    - Under water babes and moms, undated (Box 91, Hi8 437_1301)
    - Van Gogh TV, Stadtgalerie, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1134)
    - Video on Merce and John, undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1147)
    - "World Trade Center Special", undated (Box 122, Vhs 437_1157)
    - Yeohlee, tripod cam, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1274)
- Series III. Visual Art, 1960-1995; 16.5 Linear Feet in 24 manuscript boxes, 7 flat boxes, 2 cassette boxes, 1 card box, and 1 record carton; 1 MiniDV; 417 Megabytes in 72 digital files
  Series III. Visual Works (1960-1995) includes photographs, xerox art, paintings, sketches, sketchbooks, sculptural pieces, and textiles created by Arleen Schloss; photographs of Schloss taken by other artists; materials used in the art creation process, such as mock-ups, research files on various materials, letterpress transfer sheets, and source images; and Mail Art sent to Schloss by other artists, including E. F. Higgins, Buster Cleveland, Alan Rand, and Kwok Mang Ho.
  Series III. Visual Works is arranged into two subseries:
  Subseries III.A Works by Date Subseries III.B Photographs
  - Subseries III.A: Works by Date, 1960-2002; 12 Linear Feet in 13 manuscript boxes, 7 flat boxes, 1 record carton, 1 card box, and 2 cassette boxes; 417 Megabytes in 72 digital files
    This subseries is arranged chronologically, Sketchbooks, Mail Art, and Xerox Art grouped together. Undated materials are arranged alphabetically following the chronological listing.
    This subseries contains visual art pieces by Arleen Schloss, including xerox art, paintings, sketches, sketchbooks, sculptural pieces, and textiles; materials used in the art creation process, such as mock-ups, research files on various materials, letterpress transfer sheets, and source images; and Mail Art sent to Schloss by other artists, including E. F. Higgins, Buster Cleveland, Alan Rand, and Kwok Mang Ho.
    - Sketchbook, circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Sketchbook -- Figure Drawings, circa 1960s (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sketchbook -- Figure Drawings, July, 1966 (Box Shared Fales 042, Folder 17)
    - Sketchbook -- "Alphabet Letter Codes", 1974
      - Sketchbook (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Digital Scans, FA_MSS_437_ER_29
    - Sketchbook -- "The Roundabout" Installation Mock-ups, undated (Box 63, Folder 2, 3)
    - Mail Art -- Alan Rand, 1966 - 2002 (Box 15, Folder 15, Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Mail Art -- E.F Higgins, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2, Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 14)
    - Mail Art -- Various Artists, circa 1979 - 1990s (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Mail Art -- Arlan Huang, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Mail Art -- Kwok Mang Ho, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Mail Art -- "ART FOR UM" by Buster Cleveland, circa 1993 (Box 20, Folder 3, 4, 5, 6, Box 21, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4)
    - Mail Art -- R.L. Seltman, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Mail Art -- Shozo Shimamoto, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Mail Art -- Chickenman, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Mail Art -- Andy Warhol, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Mail Art -- Angela Hans, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Mail Art -- Buster Cleveland, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Words Tell, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 12, 13)
    - Figure Drawings, 1968 - 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Research File -- Rubber Bands, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Stationary Samples, circa 1970s - 1980s (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Arleen's Dance" at the Aldrich Museum, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Fiber Works, 1972 - 1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Fiber in Glass", December, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "Ceiba" Fiber Works, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Letterpress transfer sheets, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "25 Portraits of MENFP Series", April 21, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - "Faces with Electric Pencil", August - September, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Xerox Art -- "Copies of Words" and "Color Wordwork", 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Xerox Art -- "Fabric Streched", 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Xerox Art -- "Rubberbands", 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Xerox Art -- "Eve in the Fall", 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Xerox Art -- "A", 1978
      - Paper materials (Box 18, Folder 3, 4)
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_437_ER_30
    - Xerox Art -- Arleen Schloss Portrait, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Xerox Art -- Bible Photocopies, undated (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Xerox Art -- Color Works, undated (Box 18, Folder 7, 8, 9)
    - Xerox Art -- "Frame #1-83", undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Xerox Art -- Iron-on Transfers, undated (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Xerox Art -- Scrolls, 1960-2000 (Box 148, Box 150, Box 158, Box 161)
      These items must be handled with nitrile gloves.
    - Xerox Art -- Self Portraits in Color, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Xerox Art -- "Y", undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Snap" Air Brush Paintings, March - April, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Idea, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - A Postcard Story, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - "Its I", January, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - A Black Cat, October, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - "Design in the Key of A", circa 1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Hand Painted Self Portraits, circa 1980s (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - "Arleen Schloss in Amsterdam" Portraits, April, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Plastic Art Pieces, Paris, 1981 (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 15)
    - "Example of Mirror Letters", 1985 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - "Bill Ding Blox", 1984-1988
      - U-matic, 1984 (Box 123, U-matic 437_1166)
      - Paper materials, 1987 - 1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - MiniDV -- Willoughby, undated (Box 67, Minidv 437_2410)
    - Photocopied portraits with drawing, 1987 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - The Illuminated Alphabet, 1987 - 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Claudia Zólsch Photography Collaboration, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "A" by Marion Delkees, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Digital Collages, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Research File -- Plastic and Mirrors, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Domed marble structure mockup, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - "A" graphic elements and source images, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - "A" sculpture with deminted Federal Reserve chips, undated (Box 23)
    - "Alphabet", undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Alphabet graphic elements and source images, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Alphabet stencil pieces, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - "Art A-pparel" Press Release, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Calligraphy, undated (Box 61, Folder 11, Box 162)
      Rolled artwork in Box 162 must be handled with nitrile gloves.
    - Collages, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Color Mirror Sculptures, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - "Communication in Peace", undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "The E Balloon Letters" Sketches, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Electronic Marble Scuplture Mock-ups, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "EYE" Graphic elements and source images, undated (Box 24, Folder 1, Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Holographic pieces, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Lists of Artworks by Arleen Schloss, undated
      - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_437_ER_31
    - "The Logical Action Solitude" Sketch, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - "Lyric Piece", undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Sign language alphabet -- Cyanotype artwork, undated (Flat-file-folder 2)
      This item must be handled with nitrile gloves. Assistance from the Preservation Department is required to view this item.
    - Sketches, undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Test pressing Y pants, undated (Box 95, Minidv 437_1444)
    - Untitled collage, undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Untitled brushed piece, undated (Box Shared Fales 115, Folder 16)
    - "What's Your God?" Tote Bag, undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III.B: Photographs, 1960-1997; 7 Linear Feet in 12 manuscript boxes and 2 flat boxes
    This subseries is arranged chronologically with photographs and photo slides grouped together, respectively.
    This subseries includes photographs taken by and of Arleen Schloss, depicting her performances, film and video work, travels, and personal life.
    - Photographs -- Personal, circa 1960s - 1970s (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Photographs -- Portraits of Arleen Schloss, circa 1965 - 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3-5, Box 61, Folder 6-7)
    - Photographs -- Exhibitions, circa 1972 - 1985 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Photographs -- Live Installations, 1976 - 1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Photographs -- Performance Art Workshops, 1978 - 1980 (Box 25, Folder 3-4, Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Photographs -- European Tour, circa 1980s (Box 25, Folder 5-6)
    - Photographs -- Video Production, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Photographs -- Video Stills, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Photographs -- Adventure A, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Photographs -- "Letter People", 1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Photographs -- A Gallery, 1983 - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Photographs -- A's Sculpture Garden, 1985 - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Photographs -- Color Mirror Letters, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Photographs -- China, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Photographs -- "New Year", 1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Photographs -- Bremen, 1993 - 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10, 11)
    - Photographs -- Exhibitions, circa 1990s (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Photographs -- Travel, circa 1990 - 2005 (Box 27, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4)
    - Photographs -- Korea, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 5, 6)
    - Photographs -- A's Wave, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Photographs -- Apartment Interiors, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Photographs -- LFPS Models, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Photographs -- New York City, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Photographs -- Nik Williams, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Photographs -- Portraits, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Photographs -- Performances and Events, circa 1970s (Box 28, Folder 7-9, Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Photographs -- Performances and Events, circa 1980s (Box 29, Folder 1-4, Box 30, Folder 1, Box 65, Folder 23, Box 149, Folder 2-3)
    - Photographs -- Performances and Events, circa 1990s (Box 30, Folder 2-4)
    - Photo Slides -- Schloss / Kelly Acrylic Paintings, circa 1960s (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Photo Slides -- Foot Painting Figures, circa 1970s (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Photo Slides -- Ray Portraits and Travels, circa 1970s (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Photo Slides -- Rubber bands, circa 1970s (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Photo Slides -- Texas, circa 1970s (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Photo Slides -- Posters used in performances, circa 1970s - 1980s (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Photo Slides with Descriptive Notebook, 1970 - 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7-9, Box 32, Folder 1-4)
    - Photo Slides -- Paintings and Plastics, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Photo Slides -- Elastics, 1972 - 1975 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Photo Slides -- Rubber Band Balloons, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Photo Slides -- Xerox Generation Egg, 1974 - 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Photo Slides -- Alphabet A-Z Drawings, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Photo Slides -- Roosevelt Island, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Photo Slides -- Prints, Drawings, Sculptures, 1977 - 1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Photo Slides -- Mirror (Broken), 1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Photo Slides -- Street Letters, 1976 - 1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Photo Slides -- Paris, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Photo Slides -- Blue Collection Collage, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Photo Slides -- A's Performance School, 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Photo Slides -- Laser Dress, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Photo Slides -- Werner TV, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Photo Slides -- BBQ at Castle Tillysburg, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Photo Slides -- Linz Performances, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Photo Slides -- Rehearsals, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Photo Slides -- Reflextions Color Mirror, 1986 - 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Photo Slides -- Asia Tour, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Photo Slides -- Storefront for Art and Architecture, 1987 - 1997 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Photo Slides -- Cage Visit, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Photo Slides -- Luca's Marble Scuplture, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Photo Slides -- Marbles with Clay, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Photo Slides -- Portraits for Suzi's Magazine, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Photo Slides -- Cage Glasswork, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Photo Slides -- Video Sculpture with Glass Marbles, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Photo Slides -- Retrospective Germany, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Photo Slides -- Westbeth, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Photo Slides -- Gloria Schloss Works, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Photo Slides -- How She Sees It, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Photo Slides -- Stone Marble, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Photo Slides -- Barbara Staib, undated (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Photo Slides -- Dr. Wheeler Interview, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Photo Slides -- Letter Alphabet and Poems, undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Photo Slides -- "Be My Valentine", undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Photo Slides -- Portraits by Nik, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Written Works, 1970-2002; 8 Linear Feet in 15 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, and 1 record carton; 1 Quarter_Inch_Audio_Reel; 840 Megabytes in 170 digital files
  Series IV. Written Works (1970-2002) includes poetry, prose, notes, and published pieces written by Schloss, including the alphabet poetry she is known for. Much of her poetry is held in dozens of notebooks that were maintained in the 1960s-1990s. Published books in this series include A Black Cat, A Dialogue Between New York and Texas, Book 5, Words Tell, The Red Book, Words, and How She Sees It By Her, as well as anthologies and publications that Schloss contributed to.
  Series IV. Written Works is arranged chronologically, with Schloss' notebooks grouped together at the end of the series. Undated items are arranged alphabetically following the chronological listings.
  - Alphabet poetry, circa 1970s (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
  - Words, 1974-1977
    - Manuscripts, 1974 - 1977 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Audio, 1975 (Box 113, Quarter inch audio reel 437_0542)
  - "Selected ephemera", 1974 - 1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Handwritten notes, 1974 - 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - A-Z: A Work in Progress, December 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1, 2)
  - A, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - A-Z Book #5, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - A Dialogue Between New York and Texas, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - The Red Book, 1976 - 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Compositions #3-4, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - "Cigarette Burn / 76 Variations," New Wilderness Letter, September 1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - "Naxos Notes", August 1979 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - "Notes from Leutron on Crete", August 1979 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - "Talking to Myself After Singing and Stuff", November 10, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - "A Story of Wednesday at A's, by A", January 19, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - "Cheap Thrills," The Village Voice, July 23 - 29, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Adventures at A's Magazine, circa 1980s (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - A's Magazine, circa 1980s (Box 37, Folder 4, 5, Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Writings on A's, 1980s
    - Paper materials, circa 1980s (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, FA_MSS_437_ER_34
  - Book 95 -- Draft Materials, 1980 - 1995 (Box 37, Folder 7, 8)
  - How She Sees It By Her -- Manuscripts, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 1, 2)
  - How She Sees It By Her -- Translations, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - "How She Sees It By Her: About the Party", October 25, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - "The Live Performance Story from A-Z," High Performance, Summer, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - "Short Stories", 1981 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - "Short Things", 1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - "Structure of an Evening", January 23, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - "A's," High Performance, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - "Examples of Thoughts / 1. Motivation - Hysteria", January 1, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - "There's a Record to Her Madness: The Deluded Elution", July 18, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - "MST", October 29, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - "As Simple as 1-2-3...", 1984 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - "Eye = I", 1984 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - "A 2 Z in Letter", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - "Spontaneous Harmony and Word Writing Collage", 1986 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Handwritten Notes -- "For Nik", circa 1990s (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - "Interview with John Cage" PITCH, Spring 1990 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - "The Age of A!" Notes, 1990 - 1991 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - "I don't No?", 1992 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Hedda Sterne Interview, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Travel Writing -- Bremen, circa 1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Adventure A, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Visioning Life Systems That Create Healthy Resources and Transform Waste: Artists Work from their Permacultural Source, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - "A 2 Z Alphabet Works", undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - "Animal Bristle", undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - "Box #4", undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - "Box #5", undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - "Box #6", undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - "Dear Theory", undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - "Describing behavior and feelings in bodily terms", undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Eric Ambel Interview, undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - "I Am Hermes", undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - "I Don't Know Where or How...", undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - "It's U", undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - John Weelher Interview, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - "Mineral", undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Notes on video editing, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - "Red Blue Alphabet", undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Scam, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Song lyrics, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - "Spiral Alphabet" and "Iden", undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - "Two Space One Space", undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - "The World is a Collage", undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - "Xcerp From Me Saying to Me - Who R U?", undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Xerox Alphabet Works, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - Xerox Alphabet Works, undated (Box 40, Folder 3-9, Box 41, Folder 1-14, Box Shared Fales 116, Folder 22)
  - Notebook -- "Fugure", 1967 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Notebook, 1972 - 1973 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Notebook, May 1973 - September 1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, 1973 - 1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Notebook -- Alphabet poetry, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Notebook, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Notebook -- "Old and New Works for Current Performance Possibilities, 1976 - 1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 2)